[{"answer": "Not me.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Who thinks sex is bad?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, why I -- I'm just so excited to have Rush and sex below my picture --", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Penn Jillette, how are you?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "The concept is that sex is bad.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What is the concept then?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Not me.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Well, who thinks sex is bad?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Yes, I agree --", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I actually think that this does certainly -- anti-sex does start often in religion.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "-- when you -- when you take religion to its extremities?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "How many times he has sex.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "You would?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "You would?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "But there can't be anybody in the world who genuinely thinks sex is a bad thing.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Once you've said sex is a bad thing -- doesn't all of this follow logically?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "That it's a bad thing?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, sure.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Or a bad thing outside of wedlock?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "It's one of the great wonders of the world, isn't it?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, you have to -- it's very, very hard not to just be told you so.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "As an atheist, when you see that happening politically, and these are people who may one day be your president -- what do you think?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "You have to have the passion for freedom greater than the passion for you know what's right.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Are there elements of a religious conviction which you think could be helpful to somebody as a political leader?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes, you may.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Can I join you here?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I think that I always go with individualism.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "But the better way for America to go now is to collectively put all this brain power together and think, how do we keep this country where it should be, a great country?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "What has gone wrong with the American Dream?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Probably different kinds of fun, I would say.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "So, Kal, what's more fun -- working with Hugh Laurie on \"House,\" being in a hit movie, or running in the corridors of power with the president?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I would get rid of TV and I would choose between movies and politics.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "If I held a metaphorical bullet to your head and you could only do one of these things the rest of your life -- movies, TV, politics?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "One is fact and one is fiction.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Which one is it going to be?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Because you're helping real people with real substantive things.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "It's been pretty remarkable.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "What's it been like in there to be at the center of things looking out with everybody else wondering what's going on in there?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Oh, gosh.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What would you say are the common misconceptions about the president?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Do you accept that as a criticism?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "The same.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "ORGAN: What kind of guy is he when the door shuts?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "To me, all of the candidates are the same, just in terms of the policy.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Who would you most like to come up against?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I try to keep busy.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You're a busy guy, aren't you?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Well, I have a -- I'm a father of six children.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "What is rotten, do you think?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Go ahead and ask me.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "If I asked you, for example, what your view of gay marriage is, what would you say?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I feel like I just got imported into the Christine O'Donnell interview you did back in August.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "What is your view of gay marriage?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I would tell my children, as -- I tell them what I believe myself.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Would you tell them that gay marriage is a sin?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I believe that marriage was defined by God a long time ago.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What do you believe?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I think that it's -- it's unnatural.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I think that it's wrong.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "So what's your view of abortion?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Under any circumstances.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Under any circumstances?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "I think someone who is ultimately willing to murder a child, even to fix another tragic end, a devastating situation like rape or incest or things like that, is not taking the moral high road.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Even rape and incest?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "AMERON: Yes, and I will help you.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Could you honestly look a daughter in the eye if she was raped and say you have got to have that child?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "You would do that?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "I take my values.", "docId": "120302pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Whose do you take?", "qSentId": 668}]